nationalpositions.com 2013-06-21

# Privacy Policy | National Positions

_Last Updated on April 8, 2013_

Our Privacy Commitment

Welcome to National Positions! National Positions. (“National Positions,” “we,” “us” or “our”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of the National Positions websites ([www.nationalpositions.com](http://www.nationalpositions.com/)) where this Privacy Policy is posted (the “Site(s)”) (we refer to the Site(s), the services made available through the Site(s), collectively, as the “National Positions Features”). As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform visitors to the Site(s) and users of the National Positions Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site(s). By visiting the Site(s) or using any of the National Positions Features, you consent to National Positions’ collection, use, storage, deletion and disclosure of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and is only applicable to the Site(s) and not to any other website that you may be able to access from the Site(s) which may have its own data collection and use practices and policies.

This policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?
  * Will we share your personal information with third parties?
  * What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?
  * What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

_What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?_

_Types of Information We Collect_

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you. You do not need to submit personal information to access certain areas of the Site(s), but if you do not want to disclose certain personal information to us, you will not be able to access certain aspects of the National Positions Features.

We collect personal information when you create an account through the National Positions Features; purchase marketing services through the Site; work with our team to optimize the marketing services we provide to you; or receive customer or technical support.

To order marketing services from National Positions through the Site(s) and create an account for the National Positions Features, we require you to provide your name, your company name, email address, billing address, phone number, your website URL, your title and additional billing information depending on your preferred method of payment, such as your credit card number and payment method expiration date. You will also need to create a screen name in order to create an account. We also collect information about your company, websites and videos such as traffic statics, search engine rankings, conversion rates and other information related to the visibility, layout, reputation, popularity and success of your websites and videos.

How We Use Your Personal Information

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to complete your transaction and provide the services offered through the Site(s); provide marketing data to you about your websites and your videos; handle/route your customer service questions or issues; to provide you our newsletter; and/or notify you of promotions and offers. We may also contact you via e-mail, text message, telephone, or postal mail to send you messages about the National Positions Features, to request your feedback and to provide other general announcements. We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the National Positions Features. We may use personal information that you provide to us to send messages to you in response to your questions, inquiries or requests. We may also use your personal information to contact you when necessary.

_Cookies_

“Cookies” are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor’s browser and are stored on the visitor’s hard drive. Like many websites, we employ cookies in certain areas of the Site(s) to allow us to provide information which is targeted to you and to make your online experience more convenient. Additionally, analytics tools that are managed by third parties which may appear on the Site(s) use cookies. These analytics tools use cookies to collect non-personal information while you utilize the Site(s). You may not realize this information is being collected. In some cases, we may have access to information from cookies used by these analytics tools on the Site(s) and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited.

_Log Information_

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site(s). Additionally, some of the National Positions Features may collect information regarding your computer system. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and version, domain names, physical location, which National Positions Features you

use and when and how long you use them. We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the National Positions Features, to provide customer service, to maintain and improve the National Positions Features, to help prevent fraud and misuse and for other security purposes.

_Children’s Privacy_

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. We take children’s privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children’s online experience at all times.

_Will we share your personal information with third parties?_

Sharing of Information

We may use your non-personal information on an anonymous basis to provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties.

In addition, we will share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

_Protection of rights._ We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, credit card rules or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce the Terms of Use or Terms of Service, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of National Positions, its employees, users of the National Positions Features or others.

_Asset transfers._ If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of National Positions’ assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the National Positions Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you, either through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site(s).

_Service providers_. We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf, fraud prevention, bill collection, marketing, search engine optimization, sales and technology services. For example, we have partnered with other companies to process payments. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to only use your personal information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for their own benefit.

Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site(s). Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective webmasters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.

_What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?_

_Control of Your Information_

You may update or delete your personal information or modify your account preferences for the National Positions Features by accessing the “My Account” area of the National Positions Features or sending us an email to privacy@nationalpositions.com requesting us to update or delete your personal information. Please note that when you delete your account, we may retain your account information thereafter for the purpose of internal account management and fraud prevention activities.

_Opting Out of Receiving Communications from Us_

If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, e-mails or other announcements, you may unsubscribe by writing to us at privacy@nationalpositions.com or replying to the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our e-mails. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us.

_Mediation_

You also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy that you and National Positions will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Los Angeles, California with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorney’s fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

_What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?_

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities with restricted access, and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to National Positions employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the National Positions Features and provide you marketing services. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the National Positions Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.

Notification of Changes

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on this page.

Questions? Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@nationalpositions.com.

Terms of Service

Please read the Terms of Use and Terms of Service governing the use of the Site(s), the National Positions Features and National Positions’ provision of marketing services.
